so feel like we didn't got close a
little bit so I can be a little bit more
honest with child I'm going through some
new stuff in my life thank you
I'm fat and I'm broke which means I need
to join a gym but I can't afford to so
what I have to do is walk around my
neighborhood to get my exercise so I
need to talk to all you dog lovers stop
walking your dogs with no leash cuz I'm
scared and I'm tired of you looking at
me like something wrong with me when I'm
trying to verbally protect myself
[Applause]
now you looking at me like what is wrong
with you
why are you tripping big man what oh
nothing don't bite muffin don't bite
well I don't know muffin don't bite all
I see is a pit bull running toward be
free it would be the same as if you saw
me walking down the street with a gun
and no bullets what's wrong with you why
you trippin man Oh muffin don't bite
[Applause]
and then you name your dog's wrong too
cuz the names supposed to match yo dog
tired of going to your house you like
hey bones you want to meet cupcake
alright I'll be cupcake
okay get it a werewolf shuttle named
that dog Cujo it's like meeting a white
dude named Jamal
[Laughter]
Oh use your mom put the kool-aid up put
kool-aid up get some iced tea the sweet
potato pie way pumpkin pumpkin pie
that's what we here I see all kind of
ages of here old days young age cool
you're young kids you take me back to my
stuff for two teaching days yeah yeah
used to be a substitute out in LA but
then had to stop you got too dangerous
what they did was y'all can't figure out
if y'all supposed to laugh at that or
not it's a comedy show if I say it you
feel like laugh and laugh at it it is
okay y'all like oh we laugh at that yes
it's a la this provo we no excuse
so what they did was it's not the kids
fault they implemented school uniforms
to try to help the kids with all the
gang violence and all the racial tension
they like we're gonna be patriotic a tie
school you can only wear the colors of
the American flag you can on the word
red white and blue and that's cool so we
got a school full of Crips Bloods and
the Ku Klux Klan
[Applause]
you know what I will stay at home and
substitute teach I will be the home
school substitute teacher yeah when your
mama need to go to Walmart you call me
then I take over there now I was able to
learn a lot when I was serving fellas we
got to do better about teaching our
young boys to have good healthy
friendships with other other young boys
so they can help with life girls then
you got no problem I love girls friends
all the time
here's what I realized if a girl going
the restroom and she see another girl
crying she will immediately become her
new best friend she'd be like girl what
you in here crying I cut my
boyfriend cheating with helping a
cheerleader on you ain't got to go
through this here's my snapchat my
mama's Twitter at my grandmother's
Instagram yeah we gonna work this out
Ross if a boy go in the restroom
and he's seen another bar cries he walk
right back out
no I'm good I can hold it I can hold it
man I got to go no mo I'm good I'm good
hey I'll do it over Yahoo all right I
just want to acknowledge because y'all
ain't gonna get a lot of attention now
ain't got nothing to do with child it's
just that the lights they cut off right
here and I'm black so and I'm not Halle
Berry black I'm West this nice black so
if I go too far over here I get lost in
it somebody I know they sensitive just
wait till you get back in the lake just
wait we don't want our Sharpton marching
in provo we don't need this drama at all
it is what it is it is what it is cuz
that's the hot new phrase right now
everybody's always saying that it is
what it is it is what it is that's the
new way of saying somebody's about to
take advantage of you that's what that
is
cuz don't nothing good ever happens
before you hear it is what it is it
ain't nothing cool like for $2,500 for
what bump it is what it is there's
always some awkward some weird something
terrible like you show up on a blind
date you're like oh you're supposed to
be a woman
oh it is what it is this brother wagon
got no girlfriend right now that ain't
why movie prices that's why I got no
girlfriend expensive movie prices just
ruin my date lights remember back in the
day fellas when the movies used to be
cheap so you didn't really care if the
date worked out you know she's like bone
I don't want to go to the movies with
you no mo you're too loud in country I
don't care
ain't nobody scared of you my mama gave
me $10
I got a dollar left that's FOMO games I
don't get home you go to the movies
nowadays even the popcorn cost nine
hundred and seventy five dollars be like
hey girl I spend this much money on you
you gonna feed me again voluntarily or
involuntary it is what it is
okay you know it's the thin line between
flirting and stalking now it is cuz if a
girl think you kill she would never
accuse you of stalking her Brad Pitt can
be highly y'all bushes at three o'clock
in the morning and y'all are be like
this sorrow man
[Applause]
I'll show a better job with a dozen
roses and a teddy bear you like well it
would have been a lot easier if you gave
me your real first name
tymberlee
got me looking for some girl named Lisa
working at the Walmart now her husband
trip it and I want the money back for
the flowers I seat the hatch ah come on
girl let's make this work you know I
love you it is what it is girl
[Applause]
all right I see there's a little bit too
much for some of y'all I'm sorry
sometimes I take it too far I'm an
extremist like that I'm a all a nun type
of dude I don't believe in middle of the
road that's why I hate that game it's
the glass half full I don't know either
fill it up and toss it all out how about
that that's why I don't even believe in
jogging I'm either gonna be in a
full-out sprint on my lay down and take
a nap even the Lord say he'll spit you
out if you lukewarm I'm like that's
right Lord
you either Oh find it for me on ice cold
that's right Lord that's why I'm mad at
you about my looks
you should have either made me look like
Denzel Washington or Flavor Flav this
in-between is killing me okay I'm gonna
need two people laughing to tell the
people not laughing whoo Flavor Flav is
so they can be in on the joke I don't
want nobody thinking I'm doing inside
jokes in here cuz I got a group over
there looking at me right now like if he
do one mo black joke y'all got real
quiet when I say it black
african-americans I'm black call me
black
so when you say african-american I'll be
looking for a team Olajuwon to come
around a coma forget my mama from Texas
I'm black
like being from Texas - I lived in LA
for most of my adult life so I had to
get used to some stuff cuz they'll a
very diverse but Texas we pretty simple
when he got but three races in Texas we
got blacks whites and everybody else is
considered Hispanics we used to go see
Bruce Lee moves on man thought that mask
is okay kid
I know that boy named Bruce Lopez I
wanna beat up Jackie Chavez see Bruce
Lee used to do karate movies back in the
day and Jackie chick okay
never it is what it is dog it is
[Applause]
guys so my little television and movie
career being going good when he told you
I had been on the view I saw some of
y'all looking like I watched that all
the time I ain't never seen you on there
I was I was on there I co-hosted we did
hot topics which is current events we
talked about Michelle Obama had went and
visited a third grade class in Arizona
and the little girl raised her hand she
said hey we hear y'all kicking people
after country that ain't got they papers
and my mama ain't got her papers
so my thought was why do your third
grade daughter even know you ain't got
your baby don't know about y'all but I
came from a need-to-know family I didn't
know my mama's real name till I was 25
she's like my name is mama that's all
they need to know it was cool cuz doctor
eyes was on there and doctor I see your
waist size is supposed to be half the
size of yo height like I guess I'm gonna
have to start wearing heels being you
ain't gonna make me feel bad mi6 to
frame I like me I like me okay let's a
boy when I said I co-hosted on the view
somebody over here was uh was that you
okay I mean I would understand if you
say it it but the director is really mad
at me right now you like you know you
gotta stick to the script I'm like I
want to talk to people I like coming to
Utah cuz ya'll a nice little suburb town
now y'all might not consider yourself a
suburb but you a suburb of Salt Lake
City
everywhere in Utah is a suburb of Salt
Lake City okay
but cuz thank you better than my own
because Wyoming is just the suburbs
state we don't even count them fools yes
Wyoming is a suburb but Utah
that's what Wyoming is and so I try to
understand to help my dating life coach
I realized I like suburb girls that's my
problem
I live in big cities but I like suburb
girls cuz I understand suburb girls I
don't really understand big city girls
like suburb girl you go see her and she
like bone I just want to tell you I got
a tattoo I'm like ooh she got a
butterfly on her collarbone oh my god
it's so cute big city girl a bone I got
a tattoo she got a cobra snake coming up
the back of her leg with a buffalo head
on the Frog
[Applause]
[Laughter]
suburb girl be like hi I know you scared
a dog so hey I got a dog I wanna warn
you my god you get older it's a little
puta puta big city girl like I just need
to warn you I got a dog so when you come
over you come over she got three pit
bulls in a headlock
[Applause]
alright y'all need to decide how y'all
gonna clap okay if you gonna clap you
got to clap as a group Tammy leaving
people out here clapping body sell oh
that wasn't poignant there was no big
deal okay I'm sorry so I need y'all clap
as a group so I like my movie in my
television career I did a movie called
all about Steve with Sandra Bullock and
Bradley Cooper where I played a security
guard then I did an episode of My Name
Is Earl where I played a security guard
then I did an episode of medium where I
played prisoner number two
[Applause]
so a lot of people like bone how you
play a prison guard and prisoner number
two it's cuz I take my glasses off see
that makes me double-sided see like this
I could play a security guard hey Earl
you got to go to jail take my glasses
off see you like this I could play a
pharmacist drug dealer like this I could
get a bank loan yes new house rob a bank
is what it is is what it is so it was
cool I've uh I did a good job on the
view so they kept calling me back I
eventually became a writer for one of
the co-hosts so I would have to take
serious stuff and flip it make it funny
for him wasn't always easy cuz they had
passed a law in Simi Valley California
and they said if you were a registered
sex offender and you wanted to decorate
your house for Halloween you had to put
a sign on your door saying you were
registered so the register people was
all upset and we put this sign on that
door and no keys come to our house
yeah that's the boy
but we artists we already paid I do
we already did I pass it don't matter
some things that don't matter you mess
with kids you don't get to be around
kids no mo
[Applause]
you rob a bank you don't get to be a
teller
now if I was to get arrested for not
paying my taxes when I get out I should
not be allowed to ever be around taxes
again
[Applause]
I should be able to walk it to the
99-cent store and give them a dollar no
excuse me sir it's a dollar seven no
excuse me I am a registered tax offender
I can't be around taxes no mo so can you
just give me my beanie please
yeah I know thank you yeah it is what it
is
[Applause]
okay another sidebar ma'am
you were so nervous about where I was
going with that joke she had a look on
his face like I don't know how he's
gonna make that funny
I don't know he kind of flipped it okay
appreciate you sticking with me do you
something free we got water gone
just the stuff okay so love my mom love
my dad I don't know how they got
together because my mom was from the
city and my dad is from the country
anybody else got mixed parents I mean I
didn't know what to do with Bologna was
we gonna roll it up it stick a toothpick
in there to try to be boo I was we
gonna poke my fork in and then fry it on
the skillet what was we gonna do I'm big
football fan I'm so disappointed in
y'all though the answer me
just on that allow go with him yeah like
no we're basketball city we wish and
John Stockton was steal bad I don't know
who he over I played college football
for the University of North Texas
it's the Division one school that was my
mistake I should have played at a
division 21 school because even the dude
wrapping my ankles was bigger than me I
was like I'm not supposed to be out here
so I played offensive line and I was
third stream well I was fourth screen
but the second thing I put on academic
probation so that bumped me up to third
string so what that mean is I didn't get
into the game unless we was winning or
losing by 50 points which was cool for
me so we went down and played Texas A&M
so by the third quarter we was losing 53
to nothing so the coach gonna be like
Hampton don't I like the light feel like
it's time I was like man so I get in the
game and it's a dude in front of me he
is 6-8 323 pounds he wore cleats with no
socks hit me so hard I wanted to press
charges
so the next play I was like dude if you
hit me that hard again imma shoot you
like what are you doing the game is over
feel like I'm trying to impress my coach
I'm like you at Texas A&M
clearly you have a pressure coach so my
mom wanted to support me she was like
I'm gonna get one of them t-shirts that
got your number on it and your name on
the back I like mama don't you do that
you go embarrass yourself at the game
you won't be another player that could
be like well ma'am when y'all sign it
oh he down there drinking Gatorade with
the cheerleaders with the clean Jersey
in the muddy game that's him
so I maintain being a football fan I
really like Cam Newton because he makes
a football fun he plays it for the fun
of the game he likes to celebrate but
probably missed in there failed I'm like
that he had fun playing the game I'm
like NFL stop stop being like that let
him dab its coating like no 15-yard
penalty
I'm like then I think about it I'm like
at the end of the day it is just the
football game it ain't that serious to
be having a celebrate you know what I
want to see celebrate I want to see
people in real life who should be
celebrating I want to see a doctor come
out of surgery by hey man how did the
surgery go
[Applause]
I want to see a fireman come out of a
burning building
like hey did you say to baby
[Applause]
I got one moment I don't know how to do
the dougie so I can't do it so just
imagine in your head the police call
somebody they was supposed to hold would
it be so funny if I ever can learn it is
alright so I love going to movies cuz
been going to movies since I was a kid
now the problem I had they used to give
me a hard time because you know 12 and
under pay a different price but they
didn't ever believe that I was under 12
cuz I was being from age I always been
big for my I've been this big since I
was 16 weeks old I just came out of my
mama mama gave me some biscuits and
gravy
so the lady was like I don't believe you
12 so the next time you come you need to
bring your birth certificate
sounds like alright cool so the next
time I came my bro my mama she was like
let me tell you something here's 12 and
he won't be 13 for the next six months
so for the next six months you better
let him in and if I had to come back
down here it's gonna be a problem with
me and you and you know no problems with
me I paid the twelve in under price till
I was 29 years old let him go his mama
crazes mama mama the rapper or something
like that proud of y'all for what I
think I was gonna get that really
excited that we finally kind of added a
political season because it just starts
to wear on me and the problem is I'm
slice right down the middle because I
can't be a Democrat because I'm
Christian but I can't be a Republican
cuz I'm black
all right either
[Applause]
so I'm a dude that I still kind of
believe in colors like I like the colors
tell you what the baby is we don't know
what the baby
Pete is a girl blue is a boy but now all
of a sudden dudes keep wanting to wear a
pink and I'm adamant against hey man let
pink stay with the girls some dude gonna
yell laughs real man word Pete no they
don't
pink is for girls let the girls happy
let it be
we had blue good but now we got all kind
of pastels so now we don't know nothing
I mean orange is the new black we so
confused oh I ain't gonna be up here
much longer cuz I got diabetes and I'm
gonna make sure here's the thing it's
two types of diabetes one of them ain't
show fault one of them is yo fault
mine is my fault now you ain't got to
feel bad for me cuz I got diabetes cuz
trust me I earned my diabetes by the
time I went to the doctor he was like
bad bad enough to get type 2 diabetes
and the thing is when you have diabetes
and you see food you ain't supposed to
eat you got to make a decision huh is
that worth getting my foot cut off you
know what now I don't even like coconut
cake that ain't oh it's red that wait a
minute hold on
[Applause]
and the thing about it I think those of
us with diabetes we need mo help we need
some TV shows to help us like I don't
care nothing about 16 and pregnant lady
I need like 31 and diabetic what that
dude doing how he keeping from eating
very alpha cake
alright so Provo y'all real cool so I'ma
be cool here's the thing
cuz people always asking me how you get
the main bone here's the deal
my real name is Vernon fish Jarrell
Hampton okay that ain't the joke my
friends used to call me hambone then
they got lazy and just calling me bone
when I was playing a college football
they didn't think it was really that
masculine to yell out good Barnard you
need a nickname you need a nickname so
when I decided to do comedy I had to
make a decision if I was gonna go by my
government name or go by bone and I
thought it sound more cool more fun to
go by bone like coming to the stage bone
Hampton that sound fun that sound cool
can you imagine coming to the stage
Bernard fish Gerald Hampton he got
puppets
purpose
[Applause]
so on the way over here I end up having
to take a back road they was doing some
construction and it was a deer in the
middle of the road and the trip point
was the deer looked at me like I was in
the wrong but it was ok because it let
me know where I was and sometimes when
you travel like you need stuff to let
you know where you are so what I had to
figure out was whenever I get in a new
town I'm not sure I go to the nearest
gas station and ask to use the restroom
if they have to give me a key that's a
sign that I'm probably not in a great
neighborhood and depending on what's
attached to the key lets me know how bad
the neighborhood is so I went to one use
the restroom the dude had a gun attached
to the key top might do you know how to
use this I like the gun okay
[Applause]
alright alright
so I'm old school I believe in chivalry
I believe that men need to be gentlemen
so the women can be ladies so I believe
okay I really get nervous when I see
women not clapping at that
especially when they wit a man is like
this won't leave the longbow cuz I
believe a man's supposed to open the
door
supposed to open the door for later then
women you need to know how to open the
door you won't be standing around for no
to three hours cause your boyfriend
ain't with you I think man should take
out the trash women you need to know how
to take out the trash he wants a house
thinking for two three weeks cuz your
daddy ain't came and visited think
managed to pump gas women you need to
know how gas stays the last place you
need to be longer than you supposed to
that thing means to pump there I hate
when I see a woman pumping gas as a
matter of fact if you're a woman and you
pumping gas and it's a dude sitting in
your front seat I betcha he got on a
pink shirt
[Applause]